<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John McCombs</title>
    <link>/</link>
      <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>John McCombs</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/media/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>John McCombs</title>
      <link>/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Team Featured in UCF Today for Receiving Paper Award</title>
      <link>/post/ucf-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/ucf-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The UCF Today news site has written about how one of the journal papers our research team submitted to the Transportation Research Board received the the Best Young Professional Paper Award.  To read the full article, check it out &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ucf.edu/news/ucf-research-team-receives-national-award-for-study-on-combating-wrong-way-driving/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  For more information on the paper and to read it, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.johnmccombs.info/publication/20220304trr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCF ITE Student Chapter was selected for the ITE Florida Puerto Rico District 2020-2021 Student Chapter Momentum Award</title>
      <link>/post/ucf-ite-momentum-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/ucf-ite-momentum-award/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From February 2019 through February 2022, I was the President of the UCF Student Chapter of ITE.  For the 2020-2021 year, our chapter received the Student Chapter Momentum Award from the Florida Puerto Rico District of ITE (FLPRITE).  This award is designed to recognize a student chapter that has experienced the greatest momentum/improvement in the past year.  During the period, our membership increased from 5 members to 32 members, the largest growth the chapter has on record.  Our chapter also added more officer positions to help grow the club.  For more information, check out the annual report that I primarily authored that helped us win the award &lt;a href=&#34;/uploads/annualreport.pdf&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Disabled Vehicle Incident Durations and Crash Response to Identify Service Patrol Expansions and Reduce the Need for Law Enforcement Involvement</title>
      <link>/publication/20220315trr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/20220315trr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This paper was presented at TRB 2022.  The presentation is available &lt;a href=&#34;/talk/trb-2022-advancing-safety-through-traffic-law-enforcement/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Team Featured in Pegasus Magazine</title>
      <link>/post/course-correction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/course-correction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The UCF Pegasus Magazine wrote an article in their Spring 2021 issue about the UCF researchers making driving safer, smarter, and more sustainable.  One section of the article focuses on the wrong-way driving research our research team has worked on.  The full article can be read on the Pegasus Magazine website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ucf.edu/pegasus/course-correction/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; or in &lt;a href=&#34;/uploads/course-correction.pdf&#34;&gt;this PDF&lt;/a&gt; of the article as it appeared in the printed magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my website!</title>
      <link>/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my website!  I made this site to primarily serve as an online CV of sorts, but I hope to post some projects and articles/posts as well.  Stay tuned for more!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Wrong-Way Driving Detection Data to Identify Factors That Affect Wrong-Way Driving Behavior and Compare Detection Technologies</title>
      <link>/publication/20220304trr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/20220304trr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This paper was the recipient of the 2022 Best TRB Freeway Operations Committee Young Professional/Student Paper Award.  Its associated TRB 2022 presentation is available &lt;a href=&#34;/talk/trb-2022-freeway-and-regional-transportation-systems-and-operations-2022/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRB 2022: Advancing Safety Through Traffic Law Enforcement</title>
      <link>/talk/trb-2022-advancing-safety-through-traffic-law-enforcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/trb-2022-advancing-safety-through-traffic-law-enforcement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This presentation was sponsored by the Standing Committee on Traffic Law Enforcement (ACS30).  Its associated paper number was TRBAM-22-01574.  It was later published in Transportation Research Record and is available &lt;a href=&#34;/publication/20220315trr/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRB 2022: Freeway and Regional Transportation Systems and Operations 2022</title>
      <link>/talk/trb-2022-freeway-and-regional-transportation-systems-and-operations-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/trb-2022-freeway-and-regional-transportation-systems-and-operations-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This presentation was sponsored by the Standing Committee on Freeway Operations (ACP20) and Standing Committee on Regional Transportation Systems Management and Operations (ACP10).  Its associated paper number was TRBAM-22-01598.  It was later published in Transportation Research Record and is available &lt;a href=&#34;/publication/20220304trr/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  Note that although I was not the lead author, I presented the poster due to the main author being unable to attend.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAV 2021 Summit</title>
      <link>/talk/fav-2021-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/fav-2021-summit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using context classification to develop intersection Safety Performance Functions: national survey of current practices and evaluation of benefits for rural Florida intersections</title>
      <link>/publication/20211101ats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/20211101ats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This paper was presented at TRB 2021.  The presentation is available &lt;a href=&#34;/talk/trb-2021-regional-transportation-systems-management-and-operations-2021/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the benefits of using a context classification system to develop intersection safety performance functions</title>
      <link>/publication/20210602jtss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/20210602jtss/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regional Perspective of Safety Performance Functions and Their Application to Florida Intersections in Suburban Residential and Urban General Context Classification Categories</title>
      <link>/publication/20210426trr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/20210426trr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRB 2021: Regional Transportation Systems Management and Operations 2021</title>
      <link>/talk/trb-2021-regional-transportation-systems-management-and-operations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/trb-2021-regional-transportation-systems-management-and-operations-2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This presentation was sponsored by the Standing Committee on Regional Transportation Systems Management and Operations (ACP10).  Its associated paper number was TRBAM-21-00078.  It was later published in Advances in Transportation Studies and is available &lt;a href=&#34;/publication/20211101ats/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statewide Application of Wrong-Way Driving Crash Risk Modeling and Countermeasures Optimization Algorithm to Identify Optimal Locations for Countermeasure Deployment on Florida Limited Access Facilities</title>
      <link>/publication/20210115trr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/20210115trr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Roadway Context Classification Approach for Developing Safety Performance Functions and Determining Traffic Operational Effects for Florida Intersections</title>
      <link>/publication/finalreportspf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/finalreportspf/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing context-specific safety performance functions for Florida intersections to more accurately predict intersection crashes</title>
      <link>/publication/20200803jtss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/20200803jtss/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/admin/config.yml</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/admin/config.yml</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
