<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | John McCombs</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/media/icon_huf66092cce3904e6ee9e182c013f7589b_441777_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Team Featured in UCF Today for Receiving Paper Award</title>
      <link>/post/ucf-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/ucf-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The UCF Today news site has written about how one of the journal papers our research team submitted to the Transportation Research Board received the the Best Young Professional Paper Award.  To read the full article, check it out &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ucf.edu/news/ucf-research-team-receives-national-award-for-study-on-combating-wrong-way-driving/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  For more information on the paper and to read it, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.johnmccombs.info/publication/20220304trr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCF ITE Student Chapter was selected for the ITE Florida Puerto Rico District 2020-2021 Student Chapter Momentum Award</title>
      <link>/post/ucf-ite-momentum-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/ucf-ite-momentum-award/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From February 2019 through February 2022, I was the President of the UCF Student Chapter of ITE.  For the 2020-2021 year, our chapter received the Student Chapter Momentum Award from the Florida Puerto Rico District of ITE (FLPRITE).  This award is designed to recognize a student chapter that has experienced the greatest momentum/improvement in the past year.  During the period, our membership increased from 5 members to 32 members, the largest growth the chapter has on record.  Our chapter also added more officer positions to help grow the club.  For more information, check out the annual report that I primarily authored that helped us win the award &lt;a href=&#34;/uploads/annualreport.pdf&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Team Featured in Pegasus Magazine</title>
      <link>/post/course-correction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/course-correction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The UCF Pegasus Magazine wrote an article in their Spring 2021 issue about the UCF researchers making driving safer, smarter, and more sustainable.  One section of the article focuses on the wrong-way driving research our research team has worked on.  The full article can be read on the Pegasus Magazine website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ucf.edu/pegasus/course-correction/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; or in &lt;a href=&#34;/uploads/course-correction.pdf&#34;&gt;this PDF&lt;/a&gt; of the article as it appeared in the printed magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my website!</title>
      <link>/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my website!  I made this site to primarily serve as an online CV of sorts, but I hope to post some projects and articles/posts as well.  Stay tuned for more!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
